Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President Records UA002
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Department files, 1934 -- 1994; 1965 -- 1988; UA002.003; 3.9 Linear Feet
  - Department of Urban and Environmental Policy: Annual Report, 1986; UA002.003.022.00026 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department, 1969; UA002.003.022.00027 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department, 1970 -- 1974; UA002.003.022.00028 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department, 1970 -- 1974; UA002.003.022.00029 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department: Planning and moves, 1967 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00030 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department, 1980; UA002.003.022.00031 (Box 22)
  - Drama Department, 1990; UA002.003.022.00032 (Box 22)
  - Economics Department, 1959 -- 1976; UA002.003.022.00033 (Box 22)
  - Education Department, 1954 -- 1968; UA002.003.022.00034 (Box 22)
  - Education Department, 1960 -- 1978; UA002.003.022.00035 (Box 22)
  - Education Department, 1983 -- 1985; UA002.003.022.00036 (Box 22)
  - Engineering Department: Visiting committee, 1976 -- 1983; UA002.003.022.00037 (Box 22)
  - Engineering Department: Goals, 1987; UA002.003.022.00038 (Box 22)
  - Engineering Department: Annual report, 1988; UA002.003.022.00039 (Box 22)
  - Engineering Design Department, 1962 -- 1969; UA002.003.022.00040 (Box 22)
  - English Department, 1951 -- 1969; UA002.003.023.00001 (Box 23)
  - Electrical Engineering Department, 1972 -- 1975; UA002.003.023.00002 (Box 23)
  - Experimental College: Annual report, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.003.023.00003 (Box 23)
  - Experimental College, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.003.023.00004 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School, 1981 -- 1984; UA002.003.023.00005 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School, 1985 -- 1989; UA002.003.023.00006 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School: Annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.023.00007 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School, 1982 -- 1986; UA002.003.023.00008 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School: Visiting board, 1978 -- 1983; UA002.003.023.00009 (Box 23)
  - Fletcher School: International Service Award, 1988; UA002.003.023.00010 (Box 23)
  - Geology Department, 1954 -- 1969; UA002.003.023.00011 (Box 23)
  - German Department, 1955 -- 1988; UA002.003.023.00012 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School, 1975 -- 1978; UA002.003.023.00013 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Assessment of doctoral programs, 1983; UA002.003.023.00014 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1985; UA002.003.023.00015 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.003.023.00016 (Box 23)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences: Annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.023.00017 (Box 23)
  - History Department, 1956 -- 1973; UA002.003.023.00018 (Box 23)
  - Human Nutrition Research Center for Aging: Annual report, 1988; UA002.003.023.00019 (Box 23)
  - Human Nutrition Research Center for Aging, 1990 -- 1994; UA002.003.023.00020 (Box 23)
  - Human Nutrition Research Center for Aging, 1990 -- 1994; UA002.003.023.00021 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1985 -- 1989; UA002.003.023.00022 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.003.023.00023 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1986; UA002.003.023.00024 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1977; UA002.003.023.00025 (Box 23)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, 1978 -- 1985; UA002.003.023.00026 (Box 23)
  - Mathematics Department, 1958 -- 1982; UA002.003.023.00027 (Box 23)
  - Maxwell, David (Dean of Undergraduate Studies): Annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.023.00028 (Box 23)
  - Mechanical Engineering, 1959 -- 1977; UA002.003.023.00029 (Box 23)
  - Mechanical Engineering: Annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.003.023.00030 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1974; UA002.003.023.00031 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1975; UA002.003.023.00032 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1975; UA002.003.023.00033 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1976; UA002.003.023.00034 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.003.023.00035 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.003.023.00036 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1978 -- 1979; UA002.003.023.00037 (Box 23)
  - Medical School, 1969 -- 1982; UA002.003.023.00038 (Box 23)
  - Medical School-Executive Council Meeting, 1982 -- 1988; UA002.003.024.00001 (Box 24)
  - Medical School-Annual Report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.024.00002 (Box 24)
  - Medical School, 1987; UA002.003.024.00003 (Box 24)
  - Medical School-Annual Report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.003.024.00004 (Box 24)
  - Medical School-Overseers Report, 1988; UA002.003.024.00005 (Box 24)
  - Medical School, 1993; UA002.003.024.00006 (Box 24)
  - Music Department, 1972 -- 1981; UA002.003.024.00007 (Box 24)
  - Music Department, 1950 -- 1969; UA002.003.024.00008 (Box 24)
  - Philosophy Department, 1958 -- 1969; UA002.003.024.00009 (Box 24)
  - Philosophy Department, 1970 -- 1987; UA002.003.024.00010 (Box 24)
  - Philosophy Department, Annual Report, 1989 -- 1990; UA002.003.024.00011 (Box 24)
  - Physics department, 1966 -- 1970; UA002.003.025.00001 (Box 25)
  - Physiology department, annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.025.00002 (Box 25)
  - Political Science department, 1934 -- 1969; UA002.003.025.00003 (Box 25)
  - Psychology department, 1966 -- 1969; UA002.003.025.00004 (Box 25)
  - Psychology department, 1988; UA002.003.025.00005 (Box 25)
  - Religion department and Chaplins, 1957 -- 1961; UA002.003.025.00006 (Box 25)
  - Romance Lang department, 1955 -- 1969; UA002.003.025.00007 (Box 25)
  - Sackler School, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.003.025.00008 (Box 25)
  - Sackler School annual report, 1983 -- 1988; UA002.003.025.00009 (Box 25)
  - Sackler School, 1982 -- 1989; UA002.003.025.00010 (Box 25)
  - Sackler School, 1987 -- 1990; UA002.003.025.00011 (Box 25)
  - School of Dental Medicine annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.026.00001 (Box 26)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 1986 -- 1990; UA002.003.026.00002 (Box 26)
  - School of Dental Medicine, 1994; UA002.003.026.00003 (Box 26)
  - School of Nutrition, 1983; UA002.003.026.00004 (Box 26)
  - School of Nutrition, 1987; UA002.003.026.00005 (Box 26)
  - School of Nutrition annual report, 1987 -- 1988; UA002.003.026.00006 (Box 26)
  - Sponsored activities, 1987; UA002.003.026.00007 (Box 26)
  - School of Veterinary Medicine annual report, 1988; UA002.003.026.00008 (Box 26)
  - Sociology department, 1954 -- 1981; UA002.003.026.00009 (Box 26)
  - Sociology and Anthropology department, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.003.026.00010 (Box 26)
  - Urban Studies Planning, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.003.026.00011 (Box 26)
- Correspondence, 1951 -- 1988; 1964 -- 1988; UA002.004; 1.2 Linear Feet
  This series contains the correspondence files as designated by the Office of the Provost. Correspondence from 1956-1962 appear to be missing. The bulk of the files are from the 1960s and 1970s. Items within files are not in chronological order.
  There is significant overlap in types of records across previously processed material in "Department Files" (boxes 22-26), "Subject Files" (boxes 1-21) and "Correspondence" (boxes 27-30). In addition, boxes 28-30 of the "Correspondence" series were arranged chronologically (although in opposite chronological runs) while box 27 was organized by subject. As of July 2006, it was decided to not reprocess these old files but to prevent overlap and inconsistent arrangement schemes in the future.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Annual Reports, 1952 -- 1964; UA002.004.027.00001 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Arts & Science Faculty, 1959 -- 1969; UA002.004.027.00002 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Business Office, 1954 -- 1965; UA002.004.027.00003 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Fund Raising Drives (Charity), 1955 -- 1961; UA002.004.027.00004 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Funding: Miscellaneous, 1953 -- 1964; UA002.004.027.00005 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Memorabilia, General, 1960 -- 1977; UA002.004.027.00006 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Legislative Information, 1951 -- 1965; UA002.004.027.00007 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Washington Staff Services, 1963 -- 1965; UA002.004.027.00008 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Correspondence, 1955 -- 1963; UA002.004.027.00009 (Box 27)
  - General Administration Provost, Office of: Correspondence, General, 1962 -- 1964; UA002.004.027.00010 (Box 27)
  - Correspondence, 1964; UA002.004.028.00001 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1965; UA002.004.028.00002 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1966; UA002.004.028.00003 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1967; UA002.004.028.00004 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1968; UA002.004.028.00005 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1969; UA002.004.028.00006 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1970; UA002.004.028.00007 (Box 28)
  - Correspondence, 1980 -- 1981; UA002.004.028.00008 (Box 28)
  - Chronological Correspondence, April-Aug., 1980; UA002.004.029.00001 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, Jan.-April, 1980; UA002.004.029.00002 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 1, 1979; UA002.004.029.00003 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 2, 1979; UA002.004.029.00004 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 1, 1977; UA002.004.029.00005 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 2, 1977; UA002.004.029.00006 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 1, 1976; UA002.004.029.00007 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 2, 1976; UA002.004.029.00008 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 2, 1975; UA002.004.029.00009 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 3, 1975; UA002.004.029.00010 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1974; UA002.004.029.00011 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, part 2, 1974; UA002.004.029.00012 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1973; UA002.004.029.00013 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971 -- 1972; UA002.004.029.00014 (Box 29)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1971; UA002.004.029.00015 (Box 29)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1967 -- 1971; UA002.004.029.00016 (Box 29)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1963 -- 1969; UA002.004.029.00017 (Box 29)
  - Chronological correspondence, 1955; UA002.004.029.00018 (Box 29)
  - Chronological correspondence, part 1, 1952 -- 1954; UA002.004.029.00019 (Box 29)
  - Chronological correspondence, part 2, 1952 -- 1954; UA002.004.029.00020 (Box 29)
  - Correspondence, 1981; UA002.004.030.00001 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence, 1982; UA002.004.030.00002 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.004.030.00003 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence, 1988; UA002.004.030.00004 (Box 30)
- General reports, 1958 -- 2018; 1980 -- 2001; UA002.005; 0.0 Linear Feet
  This series consists of reports created both within the university and by external consultants for Tufts. Final, bound reports include long-range planning studies, feasibility studies, and action plans. Some reports are internal publications, others were intended for the wider public.
  For reports issued by the Office of the Provost to the President as well as reports from Deans and Chairs to the Provost, see "Annual Reports." For reports issued by departments to the Office of the Provost, see "Department Records." For reports issued by committees within Tufts to the Office of the Provost, see "Committee files and annual reports."
  This series is arranged chronologically
  - Final Report of the Executive Committee of the Carnegie Study (1), 1958; UA002.005.031.00001 (Box 31)
  - Final Report of the Executive Committee of the Carnegie Study (2), 1958; UA002.005.031.00002 (Box 31)
  - Report to the National Council for Accreditation of Teacher Education, July, 1963; UA002.005.031.00003 (Box 31)
  - Report of the Long Range Planning Committee of the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, August 5, 1968; UA002.005.031.00004 (Box 31)
  - Report of the Graduate Long Range Planning Committee to the Faculty of Arts and Sciences, May, 1969; UA002.005.031.00005 (Box 31)
  - Re-evaluation Report for New England Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools, Inc. April 5-7, 1970; UA002.005.031.00006 (Box 31)
  - Experimental College, Report to the Provost, August, 1970; UA002.005.031.00007 (Box 31)
  - A report on the state of athletics at Tufts University, 1970; UA002.005.031.00008 (Box 31)
  - Fund raising study, July 31, 1972; UA002.005.032.00001 (Box 32)
  - Tufts: The total University in changing times; a report to the President by the University Steering Committee, 1973; UA002.005.032.00002 (Box 32)
  - Committee on Undergraduate Education, January, 1973; UA002.005.032.00003 (Box 32)
  - Affirmative Action plan, February 28, 1974; UA002.005.032.00004 (Box 32)
  - Report on research at TUSDM, 1975; UA002.005.032.00005 (Box 32)
  - An Appraisal of Tufts University by the secondary school community, parents and alumni, March, 1976; UA002.005.033.00001 (Box 33)
  - Tufts University transportation study, 1976; UA002.005.033.00002 (Box 33)
  - Report of the committee to study the feasibility of starting a school of veterinary medicine, 1976; UA002.005.033.00003 (Box 33)
  - Proposal to the Commonwealth Fund, July 15, 1977; UA002.005.033.00004 (Box 33)
  - Health careers, September, 1977; UA002.005.033.00005 (Box 33)
  - Feasibility study report, Medical School and College of Arts and Sciences, October 5, 1977; UA002.005.033.00006 (Box 33)
  - Report of the President's Task Force on the Future of the Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1978; UA002.005.033.00007 (Box 33)
  - Mellon Grant reports, July-June, 1976 -- 1978; UA002.005.034.00001 (Box 34)
  - Physical plant policies and procedures, April, 1979; UA002.005.034.00002 (Box 34)
  - University patent policies, October 26, 1981; UA002.005.034.00003 (Box 34)
  - Undergraduate admissions survey report, 1981; UA002.005.034.00004 (Box 34)
  - Tufts Health Sciences Education Building Planning Committee reports and minutes, March, 1982; UA002.005.034.00005 (Box 34)
  - Facilities for sciences, April, 1982; UA002.005.034.00006 (Box 34)
  - Human Nutrition Research Center on Aging, 1982; UA002.005.034.00007 (Box 34)
  - Human Nutrition Research Aging Center, Annual Report, 1982; UA002.005.034.00008 (Box 34)
  - Prospects for graduate education in arts and sciences: a report to the Tufts community on an assessment of major doctoral programs, 1983; UA002.005.035.00001 (Box 35)
  - Nursing administration manual (1), 1983; UA002.005.035.00002 (Box 35)
  - Nursing administration manual (2), 1983; UA002.005.035.00003 (Box 35)
  - School of Nutrition, present status and plans, December, 1983; UA002.005.035.00004 (Box 35)
  - Community impact study, December, 1983; UA002.005.035.00005 (Box 35)
  - Community impact study, summary report, December, 1983; UA002.005.035.00006 (Box 35)
  - Physical plant, annual report, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.005.035.00007 (Box 35)
  - Computing at Tufts, development plan, December 31, 1983; UA002.005.035.00008 (Box 35)
  - Program plan summary, 1980 -- 1984; UA002.005.035.00009 (Box 35)
  - Lincoln Filene Center, five-year progress report, 1980 -- 1984; UA002.005.036.00001 (Box 36)
  - Dental School admissions study, December, 1984; UA002.005.036.00002 (Box 36)
  - Federally sponsored research, 1977 -- 1985; UA002.005.036.00003 (Box 36)
  - Affirmative Action plan (1 of 4), 1984 -- 1985; UA002.005.036.00004 (Box 36)
  - Affirmative Action plan (2 of 4), 1984 -- 1985; UA002.005.036.00005 (Box 36)
  - Affirmative Action plan (3 of 4), 1984 -- 1985; UA002.005.036.00006 (Box 36)
  - Affirmative Action plan (4 of 4), 1984 -- 1985; UA002.005.036.00007 (Box 36)
  - Sponsored activities at Tufts, 1976 -- 1986; UA002.005.036.00008 (Box 36)
  - Ballou/Bookstore planning study, April 28, 1986; UA002.005.036.00009 (Box 36)
  - Development operating plan, July, 1986; UA002.005.036.00010 (Box 36)
  - Center for the Study of Drug Development, 1986; UA002.005.036.00011 (Box 36)
  - Fletcher School, 1986; UA002.005.037.00001 (Box 37)
  - Center for Environmental Management: transportable treatment unit technologies, 1986; UA002.005.037.00002 (Box 37)
  - Center for Environmental Management: foreign practices in hazardous waste minimization, 1986; UA002.005.037.00003 (Box 37)
  - Center for Environmental Management: national hazardous waste forum, 1986; UA002.005.037.00004 (Box 37)
  - Report of the Tufts-China Executive Development Program, June - August, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.005.037.00005 (Box 37)
  - Center for the Study of Drug Development, annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.005.037.00006 (Box 37)
  - Sociology and Anthropology, annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.005.037.00007 (Box 37)
  - Department of Philosophy, annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.005.037.00008 (Box 37)
  - College of Engineering, annual report, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.005.037.00009 (Box 37)
  - Dental School: final report on research and strategic analysis, August, 1987; UA002.005.037.00010 (Box 37)
  - Institutional self-study report (1), 1987; UA002.005.038.00001 (Box 38)
  - Institutional self-study report (2), 1987; UA002.005.038.00002 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, March 16, 1988; UA002.005.038.00003 (Box 38)
  - Post-graduate plans report, March 29, 1988; UA002.005.038.00004 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, May 17, 1989; UA002.005.038.00005 (Box 38)
  - Computing and communications, five-year plan, 1989 -- 1994; UA002.005.038.00006 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, October 18, 1989; UA002.005.038.00007 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, October 18, 1989; UA002.005.038.00008 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, October 18, 1989; UA002.005.038.00009 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, November 3-4, 1989; UA002.005.038.00010 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, November 15, 1989; UA002.005.038.00011 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, November 15, 1989; UA002.005.038.00012 (Box 38)
  - Research at Tufts: Hill Campus overview, November, 1989; UA002.005.038.00013 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, February 23, 1990; UA002.005.038.00014 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, February 23, 1990; UA002.005.038.00015 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, April 18, 1990; UA002.005.038.00016 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, October 17, 1990; UA002.005.038.00017 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, executive session, October 17, 1990; UA002.005.038.00018 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, November 14, 1990; UA002.005.038.00019 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, January 16, 1991; UA002.005.038.00020 (Box 38)
  - Academic Affairs Committee, Executive Session, April 17, 1991; UA002.005.038.00021 (Box 38)
  - Important aspects of experience at Tufts, 1991; UA002.005.038.00022 (Box 38)
  - What is the one experience or individual who has had the greatest impact on your experience at Tufts, 1991; UA002.005.038.00023 (Box 38)
  - What is the one experience that had the greatest impact on your experience at Tufts?, 1992; UA002.005.039.00001 (Box 39)
  - Management Practices Finance Divison, UA002.005.039.00002 (Box 39)
  - Graduate programs of Tufts University in Arts and Sciences and Engineering: A self assessment and strategic plan for the future, 2001; UA002.005.060.00001 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Position Analyst Guide, 1981; UA002.005.060.00002 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Science and Engineering degrees, 1966 -- 1998; UA002.005.060.00003 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Self-evaluation report of Tufts University School of Veterinary Medicine, Volume II, 1990; UA002.005.060.00004 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Strategic review [1 of 2], 1992; UA002.005.060.00005 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Strategic review [2 of 2], 1992; UA002.005.060.00006 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Strategic review, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.005.060.00007 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Self Study, 1960; UA002.005.060.00008 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Tufts Self Study, summary in Tufts Alumni Review, 1960; UA002.005.060.00009 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University Self-study Report for comprehensive visit by the New England Association of Schools and Colleges, 1992; UA002.005.060.00010 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Tufts University School of Medicine LCME self-study, 1993; UA002.005.060.00011 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - University-wide Review of Graduate Programs, copy 1, 2001; UA002.005.060.00012 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - University-wide Review of Graduate Programs, copy 2, 2001; UA002.005.060.00013 (Box UA002 Shared 1)
  - Fifth-year Interim Report to the New England Association of Schools and Colleges, January, January 2018; UA002.005.039.00003; 1 Folder(s) (Box 39)
    Immediate Source of Acquisition
    Transferred by the Office of the Provost and Senior Vice President, 2018, accession UA-2018-038.
- Annual reports, 1977 -- 2003; UA002.006; 1.7 Linear Feet
  This series consists of annual summary reports submitted by the Provost to the University President as well as reports submitted by Deans and Chairs to the Provost. Additional reports issued by departments to the Office of the Provost, may also be located in "Department Records." For reports issued by committees within Tufts to the Office of the Provost, see "Committee files and annual reports
  This series arranged chronologically.
  - Annual reports, 1977 -- 1982; UA002.006.056.00001 (Box 56)
    Also includes annual reports from 1977-1978 and 1978-1979.
  - Annual reports, 1982 -- 1983; UA002.006.056.00002 (Box 56)
  - Annual reports, 1983 -- 1984; UA002.006.056.00003 (Box 56)
  - Annual reports, 1984 -- 1985; UA002.006.056.00004 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [1 of 2], 1985 -- 1986; UA002.006.056.00005 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 1985 -- 1986; UA002.006.056.00006 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1986 -- 1987; UA002.006.056.00007 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [1 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA002.006.056.00008 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 1987 -- 1988; UA002.006.056.00009 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1988 -- 1989; UA002.006.056.00010 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [1 of 2], 1989 -- 1990; UA002.006.056.00011 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 1989 -- 1990; UA002.006.056.00012 (Box 56)
  - Provost Office - annual report, 1990 -- 1991; UA002.006.056.00013 (Box 56)
  - Provost Office - annual report, 1991 -- 1992; UA002.006.056.00014 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1992 -- 1993; UA002.006.056.00015 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1993 -- 1994; UA002.006.057.00007 (Box 57)
    Transferred by the Office of the Provost, 2017, accession UA-2017-045.
  - Annual Reports, 1994 -- 1995; UA002.006.056.00016 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1995 -- 1996; UA002.006.056.00017 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [1 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA002.006.056.00018 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 1996 -- 1997; UA002.006.056.00019 (Box 56)
  - School of Dental Medicine Office of the Registrar, 1996 -- 1997; UA002.006.056.00020 (Box 56)
  - School of Dental Medicine Office of the Registrar Annual Report, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.006.056.00021 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1997 -- 1998; UA002.006.056.00022 (Box 56)
  - Annual Reports, 1998 -- 1999; UA002.006.057.00001 (Box 57)
  - Annual Reports, 1999 -- 2000; UA002.006.057.00002 (Box 57)
  - Annual Reports [1 of 2], 2000 -- 2001; UA002.006.057.00003 (Box 57)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 2000 -- 2001; UA002.006.057.00004 (Box 57)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 2001 -- 2002; UA002.006.057.00005 (Box 57)
  - Annual Reports [2 of 2], 2002 -- 2003; UA002.006.057.00006 (Box 57)
- Degrees voted, 1968 -- 2001; UA002.007; 3.6 Linear Feet
  This series contains correspondence, meeting agendas of the Board of Trustees, and votes verifying graduation requirements for Tufts students. Also included are commencement booklets from several different Tufts schools.
  This series is arranged chronologically by academic year
  - Degrees voted, 1968 -- 1969; UA002.007.041.00001 (Box 41)
  - Degrees voted, Overview and commencement booklets, 1970; UA002.007.041.00002 (Box 41)